<string name="hh01">Geographical Area</string>
<string name="hh02">Enumeration Block Number:</string>
<string name="hh03">Province                        </string>
<string name="hh04">District name &amp; Code: </string>
<string name="hh05">Tehsil/Taluka:</string>
<string name="hh06">City/Village:</string>
<string name="hh07">Cluster number: </string>
<string name="hh08">Household number: </string>
<string name="hh09">Interviewer’s name &amp; code:</string>
<string name="hh10">Supervisor’s name and code #</string>
<string name="hh11">Date of interview:</string>
<string name="hh12">Time of interview: </string>
<string name="hh13">Name of the Respondent</string>
<string name="hh14">Line number of the respondent</string>
<string name="hh15">Age of Respondent in completed years</string>
<string name="hh16">Is respondent Head of Household?</string>
<string name="hh16a">Yes</string>
<string name="hh16b">No</string>
<string name="hh17">Name and contact number of the head of Household: </string>
<string name="hh17a">Name</string>
<string name="hh17b">Contact No </string>
<string name="hh18">Name and contact number of the respondent to head of the HH questionnaire (if head is not respondent):  </string>
<string name="hh18a">Name</string>
<string name="hh18b">Contact No </string>
<string name="hh19">ASALUM-O-ALAIKUM, MY NAME IS (YOUR NAME). WE ARE FROM NATIONAL MINISTRY OF HEALTH SERVICES, REGULATION AND COORDINATION, GOVERNMENT OF PAKISTAN. WE ARE CONDUCTING A SURVEY ABOUT THE CHILDREN HEALTH IN PAKISTAN. I WOULD LIKE TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT VACCINATION OF CHILDREN 12-23 MONTHS AGE IN YOUR HOUSEHOLD. THIS INTERVIEW USUALLY TAKES ABOUT 30 MINUTES. ALL THE INFORMATION WE OBTAIN WILL REMAIN STRICTLY CONFIDENTIAL AND ANONYMOUS. YOUR VIEWS ARE VERY IMPORTANT FOR US. IF YOU WISH NOT TO ANSWER A QUESTION OR STOP THE INTERVIEW, PLEASE LET ME KNOW. MAY I START NOW?</string>
<string name="hh19-title">Check that the respondent is a knowledgeable member of the household and at least 18 years old before proceedings. You may only interview a child age 15-17 if there is no adult member of the household or all adults member are incapacitated. You may not interview a child under age 15. </string>
<string name="hh19a">Yes, Permission is Given</string>
<string name="hh19b">No, Permission is not Given</string>
<string name="hh20">Result of Household Questionnaire Discuss any result not completed with supervisor. interview</string>
<string name="hh20-title">If permission  is not given STOP interview and move to Question HH18 of this section to record the outcome of the interview</string>
<string name="hh20a">Completed</string>
<string name="hh20b">No HH member at home or no competent respondent at home at time of visit  </string>
<string name="hh20c">Entire household absent for extended period of time</string>
<string name="hh20d">Refused</string>
<string name="hh20e">Dwelling vacant or address not a dwelling </string>
<string name="hh20f">Dwelling not found</string>
<string name="hh20x">Other (specify) </string>
<string name="hh21">Who is respondent of household questionnaire?</string>
<string name="hh21a">HEAD OF THE HOUSEHOLD</string>
<string name="hh21b">OTHER HOUSEHOLD MEMBER </string>
<string name="hh22">How many members are living in this household (NUMBER OF PERSONS) </string>
